Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Public Affairs Department Records 1945-2000 (bulk 1959-1996) MS 3009-RG 19
New-York Historical Society
- Series IX. General Files, 1945-2000; 26.5 Linear feet in 26 record cartons including 35 reels of microfilm
  - Subseries IX.A. Administrative Files, 1963-1989; 18 Linear feet in 18 record cartons
    - TV-Cable Week: Closedown, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 21-24)
    - TV-Cable Week: Cover, 1983 (Offsite-box 2102, Folder 25)
    - TV-Cable Week: Issues, 1983 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 1)
    - TV-Cable Week: Move to White Plains, 1982 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 2-6)
    - TV-Cable Week: Press Conference, 1982 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 7)
    - TV-Cable Week: Press Releases, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 8-10)
    - TV-Cable Week: Prospectus, 1983 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 11)
    - TV-Cable Week: Publicity Plan, 1983 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 12)
    - TV-Cable Week: Publicity Updates, 1982 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 13-15)
    - TV-Cable Week: Q&A, 1983 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 16)
    - TV-Cable Week: Staff Announcement, 1983 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 17)
    - TV-Cable Week: Suggested Talking Points, 1983 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 18)
    - The Washington Star, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 2103, Folder 19-20)
    - United Satellite Communications, Inc.: American Television and Communications, Inc. and Tele-Communications, Inc. Venture, 1985 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 4)
    - USA Network, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 5)
    - Video: General, 1981 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 6)
    - Video: Speeches: Vincent, Francis, 1983 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 7)
    - Video: Transponders, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 8)
    - Video Group: Development [empty], undated (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 9)
    - Video Group: Warner Amex, 1985 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 10)
    - Videocassettes, 1984 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 11)
    - Videotext, 1981 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 12)
    - Visiting Journalists, 1985 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 17)
    - Wall Street Journal (Jonathan Kwitney), 1976 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Clips: 1988 June 17 (Offsite-box 3295, Folder 19)
  - Subseries IX.B. Annual Reports, 1945-1969, 1973, 1976, 1978; 0.75 Linear feet in 10 folders
    Annual Reports contains copies of the annual reports and press releases announcing Time Inc.'s net profits. The 1976 file includes correspondence about the production of the report. The 1978 file has drafts of CEO Andrew Heiskell's statement.
    Organized chronologically based on original order.
    - Annual Reports, 1945-1969, 1973, 1976, 1978 (Offsite-box 1757, Folder 13-23)
  - Subseries IX.C. Dinner Books, 1979-1987; 0.2 Linear feet in 3 folders
    Dinner Books contains copies of the booklets published to commemorate the dinners held honoring the outgoing and incoming editors-in-chief of Time Inc. The booklets contain texts of the speeches given at the events.
    Organized chronologically with the transfer form at the front.
    - Transfer to Archives Form, 1981 (Offsite-box 1758, Folder 1)
    - The Donovan Grunwald Graves Dinner, 1979 (Offsite-box 1758, Folder 2)
    - The Grunwald McManus Dinner, 1987 (Offsite-box 1758, Folder 3)
  - Subseries IX.D. Press Releases, 1965-1978, 1999-2000; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons including 3 reels of microfilm
    Press Releases includes press releases on various divisions and publications of Time Inc. Earlier files were divided by tabs into Corporate, Broadcast, Books, and Time-Life Records. Later files cover Corporate, Time-Life Films, Books, Time-Life Video, publications like Money, and subsidiaries such as Sterling Communications. Press releases from 1975 to 1978 were removed in 1980 and are represented by an out card. Press releases from 1999 to 2000 are on microfilm. The dates refer to the original materials and not the date of microfilm creation.
    - Press Releases, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 1758, Folder 4-13)
    - Press Releases, 1970-1978 (Offsite-box 1759, Folder 1-11)
    - Press Releases (microfilm), 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 3326)
  - Subseries IX.E. Scrapbooks, 1963-1969; 0.5 Linear feet in 8 folders
    Scrapbooks contain press releases, copies of correspondence, and news clippings on the subject. The Chicago Time & Life Building scrapbooks include some photographs and architectural drawings.
    - Chicago Time & Life Building, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 1759, Folder 12-15)
    - Chicago Time & Life Building, 1969 (Offsite-box 1759, Folder 16)
    - Time Donation to Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC), 1968 (Offsite-box 1760, Folder 1)
    - Time Newstour of Asia, 1965 (Offsite-box 1760, Folder 2)
    - Time-Sponsored Newstour of Europe and Soviet Union by U.S. Businessmen, 1963 (Offsite-box 1760, Folder 3)
  - Subseries IX.F. Weekly News Clippings, 1970-1999; 5 Linear feet in 5 record cartons including 32 reels of microfilm
    Weekly News Clippings contains packets of copied news clips for distribution regarding magazines, departments, or subsidiaries of Time Inc. Many packets include cover sheets showing they were compiled by Louis Slovinsky.
    Weekly Press Reports are a continuation of the news clippings packets, but on microfilm. The dates refer to the original material and not the date of microfilm creation. Not all months or years within the range are present. Overlapping dates with the physical packets may mean there is some duplication.
    News clippings in the Time Inc. Publicity Files (MS 3009-RG 46) may have been an earlier version of this practice of compilation.
    - Weekly News Clippings, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 1760, Folder 4-12)
    - Weekly News Clippings, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 1761)
    - Weekly News Clippings, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 1762)
    - Weekly News Clippings, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 1785)
    - Weekly News Clippings, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 1786)
    - Weekly Press Reports (microfilm), 1971-1999 (Offsite-box 3326)